[
    {
        "title": "Sports"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who won the FIFA World Cup in 1954?",
        "answer": "West Germany"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which team has won the most FA Cups?",
        "answer": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "How many England Football players have scored between 40 and 49 international goals?",
        "answer": "4 (Charlton, Linekar, Greaves, Owen) "
    },

    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which English cricketer has the highest number of Test wickets?",
        "answer": "James Anderson"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who won the 2011 Rugby World Cup?",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which British cyclist has won the most Tour de France titles?",
        "answer": "Chris Froome"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many people have won 5 or more F1 World Championships?",
        "answer": "3 (Schumacher, Hamilton, Fangio)"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which horse won the Grand National in 2021?",
        "answer": "Minella Times"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "In which city did the 2002 Commonwealth Games take place?",
        "answer": "Manchester"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which snooker player is known as 'The Rocket'?",
        "answer": "Ronnie O'Sullivan"
    }
]
